colorzilla.com 2015-06-23

# ColorZilla Privacy Policy

The owner of this Web site is iosart labs llc, owned and managed by [Alex Sirota](http://www.iosart.com/). 

Your privacy is very important to us and we're strongly committed to protecting it. 

Our privacy policy is very simple - we do not collect, sell or rent your personal information without your explicit permission. 

### Your Personal Information

We do not collect personal information about you when you visit our Web sites or use our client applications, unless you explicitly choose to provide that information to us. 

If you choose to share any personal information (such as your email address) with us, we will not share this information with third parties without your explicit permission, except when required by law, subpoena or court order. 

### Web Site Information

Like most Web sites on the Internet, our servers record certain information they automatically receive from the browser, such as the requested page, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, language preference, referring site and so on. This information is used to help diagnose problems with our servers and to make the sites more useful. 

### Statistical Information

By analyzing the Web site usage as explained above, we may compile certain statistical information, such as most popular or most visited pages on our sites. This aggregate statistical data cannot be not linked to any personal information, and we may share such non-personal statistical information with partners. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a visitor's browser by a Web site. The browser provides this piece of text to the originating Web site when this visitor returns. Various portions of our Web sites use cookies. 

Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change this setting so your browser either refuses all cookies or informs you when a cookie is being sent. Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that many features of our Web sites may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed. 

### Third Party Content

Our Web sites and client applications may display links to 3rd party sites or display content from 3rd parties such as widgets, gadgets, images, badges, feeds and so on. We cannot be held responsible for any 3rd party Web sites and accessing their content will be subject to their own privacy policies, which we advise you to check. 

### Changes

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time - we encourage you to review it periodically. 

### Comments and Questions

If you have any comments or questions about this privacy policy, please contact us. 

Last updated: December 12, 2011
